How to increase the volume of the sound
Next, let's learn how to increase the volume of the sound.
First, let's activate the two sleeves.
Let's do the effect of puffing.
First, we are going to make an opening sleeve.
This sleeve is a little bit narrower than the opening of the sleeve.
This way, the length difference of the sleeve can form the effect of puffing and creasing.
In the 2D tool bar, use the rectangle tool to click and drag the mouse.
Then draw a rectangle that is narrower than the opening of the sleeve.
Then press the N key to switch to the line puffing tool.
But when using the line puffing tool, we will find that there is a break in the middle.
Therefore, delete the break with the edit sheet tool.
Then the whole section can be puffed.
After that, we use the adjust sheet tool to select the middle sheet and press Ctrl D.
Put it under the other sleeve sheet.
Then right-click on the selected side and select add to side.
The side will automatically stick to the side of the sleeve.
But when we open the simulation, we will find that the sleeve on one side is normal.
On the other side, its side may accidentally stick to the inside.
At this time, we will choose to add to the side again.
Then it can be correctly identified.
After we have simulated and seen that the sides are correctly added,
use the line puffing tool to sew its left and right sides together.
When we pull it closer, we will see that
there is a pointy corner on the side of the sleeve.
In fact, there is a straight corner on the side of the sleeve,
and there is a pointy corner on the side of the sleeve.
Then the middle of the sleeve is divided again,
so it is pulled into a sharp corner.
We will fix it later.
The curve of this puffing sleeve is not particularly obvious.
If we want it to be more obvious,
we must adjust this version.
First, we select the side of the bottom plate.
Right-click and select change length.
In the direction, select both,
that is, extend to both sides.
I have changed the length to 300 mm here.
Because after we increased the length of the bottom plate,
it is equivalent to increasing the fabric,
so it has more wrinkles now.
And the angles on both sides have become straight corners.
It is a flat, flat corner.
So it won't have sharp corners now.
In addition to using change length,
we can also use extension to spread the fabric.
Using the extension tool,
right-click and press the Shift key,
and create a reference line at the end of the click.
After clicking the reference line,
you can extend the plate to both sides.
At this time, you will find that the extension plate
although it has a fan-shaped area,
the straight corners on both sides are still retained.
Because we have added a fan-shaped area in the middle,
so the overall fabric has increased again,
and its wrinkles will be more.
If we want to make a lantern sleeve,
the effect of the lantern sleeve is that
we will use the change length or extension tool.
In this way, we can ensure that the length of the other lines is still the same,
and there will be no unnecessary wrinkles.
Then we can freeze the sleeve plate,
and then we will start to prepare for the breast fold.
Next, because we have already made the sleeve plate,
we will start to make the sleeve plate.
We will start to make the sleeve plate.
Next, because we have already made the sleeve plate,
we will start to make the sleeve plate.
At this time, if we want to adjust the chest plate,
it may affect them due to the freezing of the sleeve plate.
So we select these plates in the right-click menu,
then select the anti-evolving plate and the seam line.
The anti-evolving plate will still maintain its current shape,
but it will no longer have any punctures
and will not participate in the simulation.
At this time, we can activate these plates on the chest.
After the simulation is started, the shoulder strap will not affect them.
Let's take a look here.
Previously, we used the elastic to fold the chest.
But when we look at the sleeves,
there is usually a line in the middle.
So now we select these lines at the neck,
then right-click and select the internal line.
I set it to 10mm here,
then click OK.
Then we're going to cancel the ribbon on the stitch line in the Kollegen
Then we're going to cancel the ribbon on the stitch line in the Too-Much-Forced- wasted arm.
Then we're going to cancel the ribbon on the strip.
Then apply the eligable ribbon on the newly-欵n.
Then apply the eligable ribbon on the newly- manufactu for the magazine.
The ratio of bow return should be set as the default address number 80.
When adjusting,
if you double tap on oneše,
the phalanx between the tra Lon link and this line is selected.
Let's do the same again.
When theatorium isaffeíoby the G-Kill casa,
there will be some draw effect
because we put the draw line to the internal line
If we reduce the particle diameter a little bit
For example, if we reduce it to 8
we will see that its wrinkle effect will be more obvious
There is a flexible ratio here
We can also reduce it from 80 to 70
Just like the 70 we set before
After all the adjustments
we can freeze these panels
Remember to use the freeze function more in the usual use process